We begin as any student does —
with a name, and an ambition.
The moment you enroll, aion-edu
mints you a cryptographic identity,
a key that is yours alone.
And it lays out your path: the exact
lessons, and the masters who'll teach them.
Press begin, and class is in session.
This is not a video.
The professor reasons with you, in
their own voice — and then they ask.
You answer in your own words.
There are no multiple-choice shortcuts
here; mastery is something you demonstrate.
When you've met every outcome,
the professor records mastery —
and a credential is sealed.
Signed by the professor.
Bound to the very rubric
you were graded against.
Untamperable from the moment it is struck.
It lands in your transcript — a
wallet of everything you have proven.
Each credential carries its
own proof, ready to travel.
Hand it to another institution,
and watch what happens.
Accepted — because they recognize
the university that vouched for you.
And to one that doesn't?
Rejected — instantly, and offline.
The same credential.
The trust turns entirely on recognition.
Download the diploma, and you hold
the whole proof in a single file.
Anyone — with nothing but this file and
a verifier — can confirm it is genuine.
Change one grade, and it is refused.
The seal cannot be faked.
Behind it all is the federation,
where institutions establish trust
as deliberately as they grant it.
They recognize one another.
They co-accredit joint degrees,
requiring signatures from both.
They can delegate trust,
and they can withdraw it.
And they can checkpoint the entire
state, signed, for any dispute.
A university that teaches like
the greatest minds in history —
and credentials like cryptography.
aion-edu.
Sealed in proof.